Hey!
Hey, you okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Taste good. Taste good.
Momoyuki
Good evening. We are here in Ichinoseki City, Iwate Prefecture.
We're here in Ichinoseki, Iwate Prefecture.
At the Iwate Wanko Soba!
It's been a long time!
I'm so happy to be here in Iwate.
I was descending.
And you know what?
Where is the girl from Iwate Prefecture?
Where is he?
He's at Arc Tachikawa Mori.
This is...
There's a flower garden and a ranch.
And a buffet.
And a buffet and a barbecue.
So when I arrived here.
When you arrive here and look around, you'll see it's a big place.
I want to go to the buffet!
I'm hungry!
And you know what?
I'd like to try my hand at sausage making at Arc Tachikawa Mori.
I want to experience sausage making!
It's my first time to make sausage!
I've done it once when I was little.
So maybe I'm good at it.
I'm looking forward to working with you, master!please take care of me, master.
You got it.
Like it? Sausage.
I love sausages.
I used to eat it every morning when I was a student.
Sausage?
Yes, for breakfast.
Well, let's just say I like sausage.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to making sausages.
But since we're here...
I'd like to go see the flower garden and the shop.
I'm thinking of going to check out the flower garden and the store at Ark Kenkawamonji.
Let's have fun, everyone!
Well, I've just come inside the building.
Yes, we've arrived at the place where we're going to change.
Where am I?
This place is called Farm Market.
Farm Market.
Farm market.
Yes, and what do we have here?
First of all, pork.
Pork
And organic vegetables.
Organic vegetables.
Yes, that's right.
And Kamado.
Kamado.
We make all kinds of things. We make all kinds of things.
We are a store that handles almost all of the products we make.
Let's take a look around.
At the front is the pork corner.
Pork corner
The meat is going to stand up.
Hello.
Amazing meat!
Wow, it's this big!
We're going to pull it up.
We do what we call "custom cuts".
Oh, wow.
If you want to make something like this with a big sound
If you want to make something like this...
We can cut any size according to your order.
We'll cut it for you.
That's great.
Okay, let's go to the next one.
Let's see what's next.
This is the pig we raise.
Tategamori Kogen Pork
They weigh about 120 kilograms when they're shipped out.
This is about the size of a full-size pig.
We have been raising them since they were small babies.
We raise our pigs with a lot of love and care, and we want you to eat as much of them as possible.
We want you to eat as much of it as possible.We want you to eat as much of the meat as possible.
Here is a panel explaining the various parts of the meat.
It's easy to see!
Since we sell wine for drinking and winning, we are making wine to match the wine.
We are still buying our own products, but we have planted grape vines and are making our own wine!
So, this is the second time in the morning.
Excuse me for interrupting.
I'm going to hit the lights.
Thank you.
Okay, I'm sorry to bother you.
Wow.
What's with the Western style?
Charming.
I see.
I think I can take a picture with my name on it.
Oh, sure.
Wear a dress.
You're right.
You know, for the tokome-chan only.
Wow, there are so many!
What's your favorite name?
Ribbon JarJarrah.
I can't wait to see it.
Ribbon JarJarrah, Castella Rarrah.
Castella?
Spongebob, Spongebob, Spongebob.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
Gralendor Vla.
Slad.Slad.
Glarendor Bra
Oh!
In order to the club.
It's orange gold.
That's awesome.
You say that like it's amazing.
That's amazing!
It's like something out of Sherlock Holmes.
I know exactly what you mean.
There's this wine barrel...
It's like a barn.
I don't know...
There were so many nice wines!
There's also a ball.
They're very popular.
What do you mean?
It's not the most popular stuff around here.
More...
More
It's nice.
I like it.
I was looking forward to having a soft serve ice cream,
I was just thinking how hot it was,
I was just thinking how hot it was, and he said he'd let me shoot,
Yay!
In the case of joy.
I'm so happy! So, I'll take it.
Thank you very much. I will take it. Thank you very much. Bon appétit.
This is the blueberry soft serve ice cream that we started selling on August 26.
We have a blueberry field inside the ranch,
We make the sauce with blueberries harvested from there and grown without using pesticides.
I love blueberries. Delicious!
Here it is!
Blueberry soft serve ice cream.
Yay!
Looks delicious!
One more. Thank you very much.
Wow! Looks delicious!
Whew!
I really love blueberries.
I'd like to eat them as they are.
That's for sure.
Then, I'll have some.
Bon appétit.
Looks delicious.
Blueberries, really, I LOVE blueberries.
Bon appétit.
Mmm!
Is it good?
Rich.
Mmm!
It's rich, isn't it?
I thought it would be thicker, but the blueberries are refreshing, so it goes well with it.
It's delicious.
It's hot, you know, so it's perfect with the steam.
The blueberries are really good.
Nice, pesticide-free.Nice, no pesticides.
She's a good woman.
It's all the rage now. Organic girls.
Really delicious.
Next time I want to go to the flower garden.
Where would you like to go next?
Where?
I'm just getting started. I'm going to go inside.
Oh! Finally!
I've been looking forward to this!
Again!
This is the entrance to the Calm Entrance.
This is the entrance of the Calm Entrance.
From here to the back, the area is about 1km in length and width.
It is 100 hectares in size.
100 hectares?
Yes, it is. It's a very large area.
Oh! Ryu!
Oh!
At last!
Thank you very much.
Welcome! Welcome!
Wow! It's huge!
Look! Welcome!
Finally!
There's so many!
Oh my gosh, I'm going to do it.
Now yes, it is a lavender garden and they are taking care of the lavender.
Thanks for all your hard work! Thanks for your hard work!
Hello! Good luck!
Lavender!
Yes, the lavender is at its peak in June, so the flowers are already trimmed now.
But, please touch the leaves of the lavender planted there.
Oh, you want to touch the leaves?
Yes, just touch it and smell it.
Wow, a bug.
Butterflies.
What do you think?
It smells great!
You can smell it directly, but...
Rub it with your hand.
Like that? Like that?
Like that.
Then smell it.
It smells so good!
Smells like flowers.
Oh, my God.
I like this view and this makeup.
I want you to wear a smell device.
I want everyone to smell it.
They say it smells great.
Thank you. Thank you.
Good, good, good.
The flowers are trimmed, but you can see a little bit of purple.
You can see them.
That's pretty.
Stylish, too.
Lavender. Lavender
I'd love to come and see it when it's full.
Indeed.
It's Nia's June birthday!
Yay!
Okay, on to the next one.
Let's call it Caolkateno Garden.
Caolkateno Garden.
You can see it when you go to the bottom of the garden.
Lots and lots of herbs!
Hee!
Thank you for watching!
Oh, wow! Wow, wow, wow, wow!
Wow!
Nice view!
I feel like a little girl.
Oh, my God! Really!
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, they're so pretty.
Wow! They're so cute! I've never seen this before.
It's a little feng shui.
It's cute.
Cute, what is it?
This flower is called a lantana.
Lantana?
It's a flower with various color combinations.
When you look at them, you can see the universe expanding inside each flower.
It's beautiful.
Which one is it?
Did you see the universe? Did you see the universe?
It's space!
This pretty flower.
Lantana.
There are so many amazing flowers!
You're lucky the weather was nice.
It sure was.
Look at this.
What's that?
Can we go?
Go ahead.
Gazebo!
Some people have weddings there.
I'll take the main photo over there.
Photo
Photo Spot
This is a photo spot.
Which way to look?
Delicious
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Hey, look, I was playing the sheep.
I thought you were playing a young lady together.
She's so cute.
This place is adorable.
It's really a lot of spots.
Hey.
From here to the herb garden at Shojoji Temple.
Herb garden.
Smells so good!Smells great.
Over 100 different species of herbs for sale
100 kinds
Herbs
It's so good!
Kokochan's favorite catmint
Catmint
I have a cat here.
Oh, you like it?
Don't be like that.
I like it, but don't.
Chamomile, rosemary...
Rosemary?
Chamomile.
You plant a lot of herbs that people like?
Look.
They eat too much.
Just in case.
Hey.
Commonly used in meat dishes
Rosemary.
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
Touch it a little with your hand like a pick.
Smell it.
Smells good.
I want to smell it.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's good.
Yes, that's it.
Touch it more firmly.Touch me tighter.
Tighter.
And smell it.
Mmm.
Smells good.
Oh, it smells so good.
It's not so much the smell. It's the feel.
Touch?
Touch it.
Are you sure?
Is this it?
Under here.
Under here? This one?
Oh, what?
Cute, indeed.
It glows.
It's... it's... it's... it's...
It's gone.
You have flowers like this?
They're amazing.
Almost.
What?
Like stuffed leaves.
Like a bedding.
Amazing.
A leaf
And it's got a really catchy name, too.
What is it?What is it?
What kind of name is that?
It's called Oyara's Ear.
What?
Rabbit ears.
Too bad.
No?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What ears?
Uh, okay.
What?
Pig's ears.
Hmm.
Not quite.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Bear ears.
Hmm, a little smaller.
Squirrel.
Hmm, a little too small.
So that means
The correct answer is white.
Hey, I thought
Oh, a rainbow.
A rainbow?
Yes, a rainbow.
Oh, a rainbow.
Ha-ha-ha.
Oh, flutter.
Oh, flutter.Ah, flats
Ah, flats
A. Flat
A-ha-ha-ha
ah-ha-ha-ha-ha
A tight direction
I'm coming
I knew it!
Oh, same
I love it!
I love it.
This one.
This
Parent made
nothing
Is it great?
Is it up there? I've always wanted to climb it.
The Magic Treehouse?
It's a six-story treehouse.
Oh, my God.
It's pretty cool up there.
Come on, let's go up.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
Oh, wow.
It's cooler up here.
Oh, my God!Great!
Fun!
It's so cool!
And the view is great!
It really is!
It's amazing!
Reminds me of my childhood.
This is fun!
What's this?
If it's a feather, the sheep might respond.
Oh, there they are.
Oh, wow.
Ew.
Yeah.
How's that?
The white one is Kelly.
Why is Kelly called Kelly because she kicks everybody's ass?
Eeeee!
Please don't kick me.
The brown one is Anne.
Anne is 3 years old
Anne is 3 years old.
Are you okay?
What? What?
I'll give it to you like this.
If you do it like this, you'll have to take it down.When you do it this way, you have to take a crack at it.
Cracked?
Let's see.
Kelly?
Let's do it.
Wait a minute. Can you do it?
Are you okay? - Yeah, I'm okay.
I'm good. I'm good.
Keep your hands open.
That's better.
Kelly?
It's okay. It's okay.
Thank you, Kelly.
Okay, now that we're free and clear...
We're going to take Maki for a walk.
After that, I'd like to finally make sausages.
I'm hungry again.
Let's go!
Thank you for watching!
Now let's get started with the sausage making experience!
Yay!
I've been looking forward to it!
Of course we can't do it alone, so let me introduce our teacher!
Today's teacher is Kashiwayama-sensei!
Hello!
Nice to meet you!
May I?
Yes!
Let's start! Then let's begin!
Let's get started!
I've already added the ingredients beforehand,
But there is no fat and parsley in here yet.
I'm making parsley sausage today,
Yummy!
The way you mix the lean meat is different from the way you mix the fatty meat.
When you put lean meat in the mix, you have to mix it vigorously!
Forcefully!
Like this,
With force!
Butter.
Rub like this.
Yes, I understand.
It will be very cold because there is ice in it.
So please do it in turns.
Yes, please.
Please do it.
I'll go for it.
Okay.
Wow! It's cold!
Is it cold?
Oh, that feels good!
Feels good!
Do it hard.
It's like a hamburger. At first, the process of making it.
You're used to it, aren't you?
How is it? Hashimoto Sensei.
How is it?
It's okay, isn't it?That's okay, isn't it?
Aah! Wow! Feels good!
Pretty dry.
Yeah. Put some effort into it.
It's hot.
So, mix it in one go until the ice melts.
Hmmm.
The ice is put in by hand so that the meat is not too warm and it doesn't go bad.
Hmmm...
Then, do you want to switch?
Yes.
Okay, let's go.
Okay.
Oh, you're making me squirm.
Hey.
Yeah.
Make it tasty, make it tasty, make it tasty.
That's it.
Okay, I'm calling out to you, so just do a little hand gesture.
What's the first thing you said?
"Be delicious.
Can I just say something random?
Okay.
Here we go.
Make it tasty, make it tasty, make it tasty.
Moemoe-moe-cow.
Yes, I think it tastes good now.
I still have more to write.
I'm tired of this. I'm tired of this.
Until you do this?
Until we do this.
There's more, isn't there?
There is a long way to go.
It's a long road.
This process is the secret to deliciousness.
Then, you know, flatten the meat.
Flatten.
Flatten it.
I'm good at it.
Flatten it?
Yes, I do.
I've never done it before.
Yes, and then you can do it.
Oh, no, I knew it,
If you only use lean meat,
It doesn't taste good.
Yes, I know.
I'm going to add some back fat now.
Oh, wow.
Back fat?
This is back fat.
Wow.
You put in that much back fat.
Back fat.
So, this is how you put the back fat,
Put it on top of the lean meat like this.
Yes.
It's kind of cute, isn't it?What a cute little thing, the shades.
A shade that Hikaru seems to like.
It's true that he seems to like it in a way.
He seems to like it, right?
Yeah, it's like this.
It's like this.
Yes, yes.
Like this.
Yeah, yeah.
Yes, yes.
It's time to see something cute on the screen, isn't it? Yes, yes, yes.
OK, it's done! OK!
Wow, the rumor. Rumor has it that today's sausage is parsley, so please sprinkle this all over the top like this.
I love parsley. Oh, really? I love parsley on sashimi. Oh, really?
I've loved it since I was little. I didn't know that.
I didn't know that. That's great, I want everyone to know about it. Oh, that's nice. Yes, I like it.
So, you said earlier that there is a difference between mixing the lean meat and the fatty meat. Yes.
Earlier, I put a lot of effort into it.
Now, you need to wrap the fat and parsley in the mixture,
Now, gently and gently mix in the fat and parsley with your fingertips, as if you are enveloping the fat and parsley. Yes, please.
Yes, please. Thank you.
Gently, yes. Wrap it in.
Is that right? Yes, it's fine.
Oh, it smells really good all the time. That's for sure.
Yes, that's about right. Oh, I see.
Now, next comes the most fun part of sausage making.
Here we now have sheep's intestines attached.
We are going to stuff the meat that has just been mixed in here.
One of us is in charge of turning it. One is a turner.
It is a sign that it is time to come out.
One person is in charge of turning.
One person is in charge of stuffing the sausages that are about to appear.
I see. That's great.
It's amazing.
The thickness of the sausages is unexpectedly uneven like this,
It looks difficult.
We are doing it while talking to each other.
Yes, we did.
Then, it's about half this length.
Chopped.
Then, we will make it into a sausage shape.
Yes.
Okay? Watch me carefully.
Yes, I'm watching. I'm watching.
I'll cut it in half. Half.
Half. Half.
Munch in the middle.
Turn it twice or even three times.
Turn it one more time.
Put it through here.
I don't know if I'm done.
I'll do it one more time.
Finally.
This...
Tie the ends together.
Tie it off.
The end
Then, the inside, though a little swollen, becomes a sausage. Then the inside, which is a bit swollen, becomes a sausage.
Amazing!!!
We will do this.
Okay.
Is it done?
Okay, then,
Which one of you does it? Let me do that part too.
I think that's a good idea. Okay, well, I'm holding it down,
Yes, please. Here we go.
Oh, here they come. Here they come.
Just go a little further. Don't worry, don't worry.
It's quite tiring. Oh, you've suddenly gotten faster.
But you're good at it. Good at it? Really?
I have a chance. No, no, no.
Just be patient with the thin part. Okay.
I'm getting to the point where I don't want to do this. Oh, man, they're piling on.
Is it this long? I've been making it longer to begin with.
The thickness is about that much.
It's pretty heavy. It's heavy.
You're pretty good at it. Wow!
Do you see the flesh? There's a meaty look.
More.
Let's stop for a second.
Please stop.
Pull back with a view.
Pull with a whoosh.
Yes.
Cut in the middle.
Here we go. Ready,
Next! Next!
And remember what I said earlier?
First, half.
Yes, half.
Half.
And then, gently...
Like this.
Yes.
A little more? A little more.
One more time.
About this much?
Yes. Then twist two or three times.
Twist. One.
Oh, you're good.
One, two, three.
Yes.
And then, yes.
Pinch about this much.
Be gentle there, too.
Gently.
And,
Third time.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, come on, ah.
Twist it about 2 times.
Yes. You're good.
One, two.
Oh, the bottom overlaps.
Yes.
And yes.And so it is.
Oh.
And, yes.
I can say.
Correct.
Excellent.
I can say it.
You want to do it? I'll do it!
This is something like Ginia-chan's arrangement.
It's true, the members usually do it.
I'm going to go.
Around here? Yes, it is.
If you push too hard, it will burst like this.
Oh, no, no, no.
One, two, three.
This flat? Press here.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
And this course?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, oh.
Then you can get in here.
Okay, I'm in.
Good luck! Oh, it's done!
Okay, it's done. Shall we do it again?
That's fine, or you can just close it right there.
Do you want to do it again? I'll do it first.
I'll do it first.
Excuse me.If you'll excuse me.
Please tie up here at the end.
Here.
Then I'll
I'm going to cut and tie it. Squeeze it more.
Squeeze it more.
Yes, that's right.
Yes, it's done.
Wow!
It's done!
Finished!
Yes! It's done!
Next, we'll move on to the hot water process.
Well, goodbye!
Bye!
OK!
Okay, 20 minutes.
20 minutes!
Okay, 20 more minutes.
Gong!
That was a little fast.
That was fast.
Ta-da!
Forty-five seconds to go.
Yes, sir.
How do you like that?
Ta-da!Ta-da!
When you get to the last 30 seconds...
Shall we turn it a little?
Yes, sir.
Okay, okay. It's 30 now.
That's great. We made our own sansage.
Here's the countdown.
Six, five, four, three, two, one.
It's done.
It's done!
Well then, since we're here, let's try it.
Ready?
Ta-da!
Sansage!
Now, take this out to sample.
This may be a little hot.
But can you cut it like this?
Sansage.
It's not shaped like this.
That's right.
Over here.
It's done.
Now, I'd like to try this one.
I think this is probably the best sausage I've ever tasted.
Please, taste it.
Are you sure?
I'm looking forward to it.
Go ahead and do it with your hands.
Are you sure?
Can we eat it now? Can we eat this now?
You can eat it now.
Really?
Yes, it is.
If you could just taste it.
That's great.
Well, go ahead.
Bon appétit.
I'll take a slice.
Wow.
You can eat it now.
It's warm
Amazing.
First time.
This is a freshly made sausage.
Bon appétit!
Ready?
Mwah!
How is it?
The meat is amazing.
Mmm.
Is it meaty?
Yes, it's good.
It's delicious.
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
Very tasty.
I'm going to try the sausage you two made.I'd love to try the sausage you two made!
What do you think?
How is it?
It's good.
Which one is better?
I can really smell the melmagallon.
It's good.
I can feel the love.
It's delicious.
It's the best sausage I've ever had.
It's the best.
The most delicious!
So, I just had a freshly made sausage.
Yay!
How did you like it?
Well, to say that it was a great success would be an understatement.
I didn't expect such a delicious sausage.
Oh, I see.
What was your score? I was.
It was a perfect score of 100.
Wow! Yay!
Is this sausage experience open to the general public if they make a reservation?
Yes, it is. It is completely by reservation only.
The reason for this is that it requires a lot of preparation.
We have to salt the meat, prepare the lamb, and so on,
We receive reservations as early as a week in advance.Well, we also receive reservations about a week in advance.
Yes, one week in advance, everyone.
Please come.
It was a lot of fun.
Also, today, I saw the garden, the last garden, and had soft ice cream,
I also had soft ice cream.
I hope you will all come and visit us.
Thank you very much for watching today.
Thank you very much.
I hope you all come to the sausage-making experience.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on!
Bye bye.